<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Morven's Life</title><link>https://morven.life/en/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Morven's Life</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://morven.life/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy Istio Multcluster in IBM Cloud Private clusters using Gateway</title><link>https://morven.life/en/posts/istio-multicluster-with-gateway-in-icp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://morven.life/en/posts/istio-multicluster-with-gateway-in-icp/</guid><description>Multicluster feature was introduced in the Istio 0.8 release, which allows the extension of the service mesh across multiple Kubernetes clusters. The primary goal of Istio multicluster is to manage a mesh composed of services running within more than one cluster but with all of the services running under a single administrative control. With Istio multicluster mesh, the location of the service deployment is transparent to the client and all services are the same.</description></item><item><title>Diving into Kubernetes MutatingAdmissionWebhook</title><link>https://morven.life/en/posts/diving-into-kubernetes-mutating-admission-webhook/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://morven.life/en/posts/diving-into-kubernetes-mutating-admission-webhook/</guid><description>Update: With the latest changes in the source code repository for this tutorial, I replaced the webhook server certificate created by the CertificateSigningRequest API and CA bundle patch process with self-generated CA and certificate, all the process will be done in the webhook server pod, so we won’t need the manual certificate creating and patch steps.
Admission controllers are powerful tools for intercepting requests to the Kubernetes API server prior to persistence of the object.</description></item></channel></rss>